<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 Richard Hughes <richard@hughsie.com> -->
<!--
This file is part of PDF Arranger which is released under the GNU General Public
License version 3 or later.
See file COPYING or go to <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/> for full license details.
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.github.jeromerobert.pdfarranger</id>
  <name>PDF Arranger</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">PDF 편집기</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">PDF uređivač</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">PDF-rendező</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">PDF Düzenleyici</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Arranjador de PDF</name>
  <summary>PDF Merging, Rearranging, Splitting, Rotating and Cropping</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Fusionador, arranjador, divisor, rotador i retallador de PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Program pro sloučení, přeuspořádání, rozdělení, otočení a oříznutí PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">PDFs zusammenfügen, umsortieren, trennen, rotieren und zuschneiden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Συγχώνευση, αναδιάταξη, διαχωρισμός, περιστροφή και περικοπή αρχείων PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Mezcle, reordene, divida, rote y recorte documentos PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Yhdistä, järjestele, jaa, käännä ja rajaa PDF-tiedostoja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Fusionner, réorganiser, découper, pivoter et recadrer des documents PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Sjedinjavanje, preraspoređivanje, rastavljanje, okretanje i obrezivanje PDF dokumenata</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">PDF egyesítése, átrendezése, felosztása, elforgatása és körülvágása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een programma voor het samenvoegen, herordenen, opsplitsen, draaien en bijsnijden van pdf-bestanden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Forrit til að sameina, endurraða, skipta upp, snúa og skera utan af síðum í PDF-skjölum</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Aplicação para juntar, organizar, separar, rodar e recortar ficheiros PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Приложение для объединения, изменения порядка страниц, разделения, вращение и обрезки документов PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Grafický nástroj na manipuláciu s PDF</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Slå samman, arrangera om, dela, rotera och beskär PDF filer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">PDF를 합치기, 재정렬, 나누기, 회전하거나 잘라내기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">PDF Birleştirme, Yeniden Düzenleme, Bölme, Döndürme ve Kırpma</summary>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.jeromerobert.pdfarranger.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <description>
    <p>
      PDF Arranger is a small application, which helps the user to merge or split pdf
      documents and rotate, crop and rearrange their pages using an interactive and
      intuitive graphical interface.
    </p>
    <p>
      It is a frontend for pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="ca">
      El PDF Arranger és una aplicació petita, que ajuda l'usuari a fusionar o dividir els
      documents PDF i girar, escapçar i reorganitza les seves pàgines utilitzant una
      interfície interactiva, gràfica i intuïtiva.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">
        És una interfície per pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="el">
      Το PDF Arranger είναι μια μικρή εφαρμογή, που βοηθά τον χρήστη να συγχωνεύσει η
      να διαχωρίσει αρχεία τύπου PDF και να περιστρέψει, περικόψει η αναδιατάξει τις
      σελίδες τους χρησιμοποιώντας ένα διαδραστικό και διαισθητικό γραφικό περιβάλλον.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="el">
      Είναι ένα γραφικό περιβάλλον για το pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="es">
      PDF Arranger es una pequeña aplicación que ayuda al usuario a fusionar o dividir
      documentos pdf y rotar, recortar y reorganizar sus páginas usando una interfaz
      gráfica interactiva e intuitiva.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">
      Es una interfaz para pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="fr">
      PDF Arranger est une petite application qui aide l’utilisateur à fusionner ou découper des documents PDF et pivoter, recadrer et réarranger leurs pages en utilisant une interface graphique intuitive.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      Il s’agit d’une interface pour pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="hr">
      PDF uređivač je mali program koja pomaže korisniku sjediniti ili rastaviti
      pdf dokumente te okretati, obrezati i preurediti stranice tih dokumenata pomoću
      interaktivnog i intuitivnog grafičkog sučelja.
     </p>
     <p xml:lang="hr">
       Radi se o sučelju za pikepdf.
     </p>

    <p xml:lang="hu">
      A PDF-rendező egy kis alkalmazás, amely egy interaktív és intuitív grafikus 
      felület segítségével segíti a felhasználót a pdf dokumentumok egyesítésében 
      vagy felosztásában, valamint az oldalak elforgatásában, kivágásában és 
      átrendezésében.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">
      Ez a pikepdf kezelőfelülete.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="is">
      PDF Arranger er lítið forrit sem hjálpar notendum að sameina eða skipta upp PDF-skjölum, auk þess að hægt er að endurraða, skera utan af eða snúa stökum síðum í þeim með einföldu gagnvirku viðmóti.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="is">
      Þetta er viðmót fyrir pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="ko">
      PDF 편집기는 사용자가 PDF 문서를 합치거나 나누고 페이지를 재정렬할 수 있는 다기능 그래픽 인터페이스를 사용하는 간단한 프로그램입니다.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">
      pikepdf를 기반으로 합니다.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="pt">
      O PDF Arranger é uma pequena aplicação, que ajuda o utilizador a juntar ou dividir
      documentos pdf e a rodar, recortar e reorganizar as suas páginas usando uma
      interface gráfica interativa e intuitiva.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">
      É uma interface gráfica para o pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="nl">
      PDF Arranger is een klein programma waarmee pdf-bestanden kunnen worden gedraaid,
      bijgesneden, opgesplitst en pagina's worden herordend, allemaal vanuit een intuïtief,
      grafisch venster.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">
      Het is een frontend voor pikepdf.
    </p>

        <p xml:lang="ru">
      PDF Arranger - это небольшое python-gtk приложение, которое помогает пользователю
      объединять или разделять документы PDF, а также вращать, обрезать и изменять порядок
      страниц с помощью интерактивного и интуитивно понятного графического интерфейса.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">
      Это клиентский интерфейс для pikepdf.
    </p>

    <p xml:lang="tr">
      PDF Arranger, kullanıcının etkileşimli ve sezgisel bir grafiksel arayüz kullanarak
      PDF belgelerini birleştirmesine veya bölmesine ve sayfalarını döndürmesine,
      kırpmasına ve yeniden düzenlemesine yardımcı olan küçük bir uygulamadır.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">
      pikepdf için bir önyüzdür.
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/pdfarranger/pdfarranger</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://github.com/pdfarranger/pdfarranger/raw/main/data/screenshot.png</image>
      <caption/>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>jeromerobert@gmx.com</update_contact>
  <releases>
    <release date="2022-11-27" version="1.9.2"/>
    <release date="2022-09-24" version="1.9.1"/>
    <release date="2022-09-17" version="1.9.0"/>
    <release date="2021-12-25" version="1.8.2"/>
    <release date="2021-12-10" version="1.8.1"/>
    <release date="2021-11-13" version="1.8.0"/>
    <release date="2021-03-13" version="1.7.1"/>
    <release date="2021-01-24" version="1.7.0"/>
    <release date="2020-08-01" version="1.6.2"/>
    <release date="2020-07-31" version="1.6.1"/>
    <release date="2020-07-15" version="1.6.0"/>
    <release date="2020-05-16" version="1.5.3"/>
    <release date="2020-05-16" version="1.5.2"/>
    <release date="2020-04-20" version="1.5.1"/>
    <release date="2020-04-14" version="1.5.0"/>
    <release date="2020-03-16" version="1.4.2"/>
    <release date="2020-02-09" version="1.4.1"/>
    <release date="2020-01-26" version="1.4.0"/>
  </releases>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/pdfarranger/pdfarranger/issues</url>
</component>
